「岛市老八万恶之源」三语字幕
Subtitle by Sam Toki
Wed, Sep 23, 2020
「岛市老八 之 第二次厕所大战」
"LAOBA IN TOILET WAR Ⅱ"
「ラオバ の 第二次トイレ大戦」
老铁们啊,
My fellow brothers,
みんな,
呃, 虽然不是同一时间, 但是同一个彻硕儿(厕所).
Though not the same time, it is the same toilet.
同じ時間じゃないけど, 同じトイレがあった.
老八我再次挑战一把吃粑粑(吃屎) 啊.
I, Laoba, gonna challenge eating shit again.
俺はな, 糞を食べることを二度挑戦するんだ.
奥利给(意义不明), 干了! 兄弟们!
Oligay (Unknown Meaning). Just do it, bro!
オリゲー(意味不明), 食べてやろう!
呕—— 呕—— 咳! 咳…
(DISGUSTED)
(気持ち悪かった)
「岛市老八 之 第三次厕所大战」
"LAOBA IN TOILET WAR Ⅲ"
「ラオバ の 第三次トイレ大戦」
老铁们啊, 还是那句话!
Okay, guys, let me repeat that again!
諸君, 同じ言葉だ!
只有你们想不到的, 就没有我老八做不到的!
There is nothing "impossible" in my dictionary!
俺の辞書には, 「不可能」の三文字は有り得ない!
你们不要笑我狼狈不堪, 我也可以笑你,
You don't try to make fun of my shame, I can also laugh at you,
俺のことを笑うな. だって俺はお前らを笑うのができるーー
离开你的父母, 比我吃屎都难!
cuz it'd be more frustrating for you to become independent, than my eating shit!
お前らの両親を離れることより, 俺の糞を食べるのはもっと簡単だ!
奥利给! 干了! 兄～弟们!!
Oligay! Gonna have it, bro!!
オリゲー! いただき!!
↑
(明显是泥土)
(OBVIOUSLY MUD BUT NOT SHIT)
(泥であった)
呕—— 呕——! 啊… 咳! 噗! 啊… 噗! 呕… 咳, 咳!
(DISGUSTED)
(気持ち悪かった)
「岛市老八 之 第一次厕所大战」
"LAOBA IN TOILET WAR Ⅰ"
「ラオバ の 第一次トイレ大戦」
老铁们啊,
My fellow brothers,
諸君,
只有你们想不到的, 没有老八做不到的啊.
There is nothing I can't do here.
この世には, 俺ができないことがないんだ.
还是那句话 (?),
I'd repeat again (?),
同じ言葉で (?),
今天我老八, 挑战一把吃粑粑.
Today I'm gonna challenge eating shit.
今日俺は, 糞を食べてみる.
兄弟们, 奥利给! 干啦!!
Guys, Oligay! Dash it!!
みんな, オリゲー! やろう!!
↑
(第一次可能是真屎)
(MAYBE REAL SHIT)
(本物の糞であるかもしれません)
呕, 呕——! 呕…
(DISGUSTED)
(気持ち悪かった)